Narrator: More sophisticated emotions
Adjectives to describe emotions
Happiness
Narrator: 1
F: Both ecstatic and overjoyed are possible.
Narrator: 2
M: Pleased is correct.
Narrator: 3
F: Both contented and satisfied are possible.
Narrator: 4
M: Exhilarated is correct.
Narrator: 5
F: Upbeat is correct.
Narrator: Sadness
Narrator: 1
M: Devastated isn’t possible.
Narrator: 2
F: Gutted isn’t possible.
Narrator: 3
M: Wistful isn’t possible.
Narrator: 4
F: Listless isn’t possible.
Narrator: 5
M: Upset isn’t possible.
Narrator: Anger
Narrator: 1
F: Livid is the best option. Exasperated is possible. Cross is wrong.
Narrator: 2
M: Peeved is the best option. Indignant is possible. Outraged is wrong.
Narrator: 3
F: Resentful is the best option. Offended is possible. Livid is wrong.
Narrator: 4
M: Frustrated is the best option. Peeved and displeased are wrong.
Narrator: 5
F: Irate is the best option. Incensed is possible. Cross is wrong.
Narrator: Fear and anxiety
Narrator: 1
M: panic-stricken
Narrator: 2
F: rattled
Narrator: 3
M: aghast
Narrator: 4
F: wary
Narrator: 5
M: uneasy